broadbandsports.com 2001-02-02

# BROADBAND SPORTS

We are as hard-core about protecting your privacy as we are in serving your sports interests.

Broadband Sports has created privacy policies to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy. The following discloses how we use information we collect from you. If you have any questions regarding this information or our privacy practices, please see the section entitled "Questions?" at the bottom of this page. 

**What information do we collect? How do we use it?**

All of the information you provide us is completely voluntary and you are not obligated to give us any personal information if you do not desire to do so.

We request that you give us contact information (like your name and e-mail address) when you register on our site, order products, fill out surveys or enter contests. We use this contact information in a variety of ways. We use it to send you information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. You may opt out of receiving future mailings from us and our partners by following the steps in the section entitled "How do you opt out?" (below). We also use the contact information to process any orders you place on the site and to contact you when necessary.

We collect financial information (like your credit card number) when we need to bill you for products or services you order from us. We consider your financial information highly confidential and do not share your financial information with any third party that is not involved in fulfilling your order.

We collect demographic and profile information (like your zip code, favorite athlete, age and income level) to allow us to tailor your experience at our site. With this information, we can show you content we think you might be interested in and display the content according to your preferences. We share this information with our advertisers as well, but only on an aggregated basis (which means that none of your personally identifiable information is associated with the demographic information we give the advertisers).

We retain your IP address and use it to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our site. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information.

We also add to the information you provide us with information from some of our partners to provide you with the best possible experience while visiting our site.

**How do we protect customer information?**

We have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information you provide us. Certain areas of the site such as user profile, login and store checkout are encrypted to secure information exchanged between your computer and our servers. We also have security technologies implemented to protect your information stored by our servers. 

**What about "cookies"?**

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site and for other similar purposes to maximize your enjoyment of our site. In addition, ads displayed on our site may contain cookies. Cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad companies and we do not have access to this information. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that.

**How do you opt out? How do you change the information we have for you?**

We give you the opportunity to opt out of receiving communications from us and our partners. You may request that your information be removed from our database and that we do not send you future communications by:

sending an e-mail to: |      | help@broadbandsports.com  
---|---|---  
sending a letter to: |   | Customer Service  
  |   | 2120 Colorado Avenue, Suite 200  
Santa Monica, CA 90404   
calling Customer Service at: |   |  (888) 567-2757  
  |   |    
  
You may also change or modify any information you previously provided us by using any of the methods above.

**Is there other privacy information you should know?**

Our site contains links to other sites that we do not control. We do not have information regarding the privacy practices of all of these sites and are not responsible for their privacy practices. Please make sure you are comfortable with the privacy practices of every site you visit before providing the site with your personal information.

We make chat rooms and message boards available to you. Please remember that we cannot control the information that is shared by users and that any information that is disclosed in these areas by you becomes public information.  Please exercise discretion and caution when deciding to disclose your personal information in these areas.

**Questions?**

If you have any questions about our privacy practices or your dealings with our site, please do not hesitate to contact:

Customer Service  
2120 Colorado Avenue, Suite 200  
Santa Monica, CA 90404  
(888) 567-2757  
help@broadbandsports.com
  |   
| 

Here at Broadband Sports, we are committed to you and to protecting your privacy rights.  The information we collect about you is used to provide you with a more personalized and richer experience while visiting our network of web sites, including Athletes Direct, Sports Writers Direct, Roto News Direct, and Sports Authentics Direct (the "Broadband Sports Network").

As such, we have established and implemented this privacy policy to inform our members, visitors, and the parents of children using or visiting the Broadband Sports Network how we use and protect the information that we collect.  If you have any questions regarding this information or our privacy practices, please see the section entitled "Questions? Contact Us" at the end of this privacy statement.

**WHAT INFORMATION DOES BROADBAND SPORTS COLLECT?**

**Personal Information**

You may visit and use many features on the Broadband Sports Network without completing any registration at all. However, in order to order products, complete surveys, enter contests and sweepstakes, participate in polls, online chats and forums, or enter other enhanced, member areas of the Broadband Sports Network, we may require you to provide us with certain contact and/or demographic information and/or to become a registered member of certain divisions of the Broadband Sports Network.  When you become a registered member, we require you to provide us with your contact information (including your name and email address), date of birth, gender and zip code, as well as to create a password.  As our goal is to make your experience as easy and enjoyable as possible throughout the entire Broadband Sports Network, this contact information is shared among the various divisions of the Broadband Sports Network, although at this time separate registration may be necessary.

**Credit Card Information**

If you purchase any products on the site, you will additionally need to provide us with your credit card and shipping information.

**IP Address**

An IP address is a number that’s automatically assigned to your computer whenever you’re surfing the Web.  We retain your IP address in order to help us diagnose problems with our servers, to administer our sites, to help identify you and your shopping cart, to gather broad anonymous demographic information (such as the number of visitors from a geographic area), to enforce compliance with the Broadband Sports Network terms and conditions or otherwise in order to protect our services, sites, customers, or others.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small bits of electronic information that a web site can transfer to a visitor’s hard drive to help tailor and keep records of his or her visit to the site.  The use of cookies is standard on the Internet and many web sites use them.  Cookies allow web site operators to better customize visits to the site to the visitor’s individual preferences.  For example, we use cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and to provide you with a better surfing experience and maximize your enjoyment of the Broadband Sports Network. However, we do not save any password information in cookies. We may additionally use “web bugs” or other similar data collection programs to collect information to provide you with a more enjoyable and easier experience on the Broadband Sports Network. In addition, banner advertisements displayed on our site may contain cookies.  The companies who serve our banner advertisements transfer cookies independent of us, and, as such, we do not control the use of such cookies and in many instances have no access to the information collected by them. 

Although most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, you can usually change your browser to prevent that or to notify you when you are sent a cookie.  This gives you the chance to decide whether or not to accept the cookie.  Even without accepting a cookie, you can still access many of the features on the Broadband Sports Network. However, some parts of the Broadband Sports services will not function properly or may be considerably slower if you refuse cookies.  For example, without cookies, you may experience delays and may have difficulty completing shopping transactions, entering contests, or playing games. If you would like more information about cookies, we suggest you visit [http://www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/).

**HOW DOES BROADBAND SPORTS USE THE INFORMATION IT COLLECTS?**

**Personal Information**

We use the information we collect to tailor your experience in the Broadband Sports Network by displaying content according to your interests and preferences, providing a faster method for you to submit information to us and receive back the information or products you desire, sending you information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners, and allowing us to contact you, if necessary. If at any time you would rather not receive information from us, or would like to opt-out of any other service we provide, simply follow the steps in the section entitled "How do you opt out? How do you change the information we have for you?" Notwithstanding the manner in which Broadband Sports uses such information, we will not provide any such personally identifiable information to any third parties without your express written consent.

**Credit Card Information**

All credit card related information you provide to us when ordering any products or services from the Broadband Sports Network is maintained by us as highly confidential, and we will not share such credit card related information with any third parties that are not involved in fulfilling your order.

**E-mail Notification**

We may use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about new services on the Broadband Sports Network, special offers we think you’ll find valuable and important functionality changes to the web site. If you would rather not receive this information, or would like to opt-out of any other information request or distribution, simply submit such a request to us at [support@broadbandsports.com](mailto:support@broadbandsports.com).  Members may also receive electronic newsletters from one or more divisions of the Broadband Sports Network.  If you would rather not receive any of these newsletters, you may click on the link at the end of the newsletter, or notify us at [newsletter@broadbandsports.com](mailto:newsletter@broadbandsports.com). 

**Disclosure to Third Parties**

Subject to your express opt-in approval, we may share your personally identifiable information with third parties, including telemarketers and e-commerce partners, who assist Broadband Sports by providing services to users of the Broadband Sports Network. We also may share your personally identifiable information at any time if compelled to do so in order to comply with any applicable law or valid legal process.

Should you change your mind about the information you’ve provided to us or should your information change, we have provided a way for you to correct, update or remove the personal information you gave us. You can do this simply by contacting us in any of the simple ways set forth below in the section entitled “ How do you opt out? How do you change the information we have for you?” 

**HOW DO WE PROTECT CUSTOMER INFORMATION?**

We implement a variety of security measures to ensure the security of your personal information on our systems. Member personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of employees who have special access rights to such systems. Any sensitive/credit information you supply us is transmitted and protected via Secure Socket Layer technology and HTTPS protocol and then encrypted into our databases to be accessed only as stated above.

To ensure compliance with updated security technology, we recommend using one of the following browsers, each of which can be downloaded free of charge: Netscape Navigator ([http://www.netscape.com](http://www.netscape.com/)), or Microsoft Internet Explorer (<http://www.microsoft.com/ie>).  To ensure the highest level of security available today, we suggest that you choose the 128-bit encryption version from the download options.  If you do not have access to a browser that supports at least 48-bit encryption, your information may not be processed by our servers, or may not be securely transferred through your web browser to our servers.

Unfortunately, when you submit information to us (or to any other web site) over the Internet, the information may travel over many networks and systems that are not under our control and, during such time, can be intercepted.  As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Broadband Sports can’t ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.  Further, anything you voluntarily provide in any public area of the Internet, including on the Broadband Sports Network, will be publicly available to other visitors on that web site and potentially to other third parties, and you should always exercise caution when deciding to publicly disclose any of your personal information.

**HOW DO YOU OPT OUT? HOW DO YOU CHANGE THE INFORMATION WE HAVE FOR YOU?**

We give you the opportunity to opt out of receiving communications from the Broadband Sports Network.  To request that your information be removed from our database or that certain information previously provided to us be updated or modified, or that we not send you any future communications, simply contact us in any of the following manners: 

| 

Send an e-mail to:

|  | 

---|---|---  
  
Send a letter to:

|  | 

Broadband Sports

Customer Service  
  
|  | 

2120 Colorado Avenue, Suite 200  
Santa Monica, CA 90404   
  
Call Customer Service at:

|  | 

(888) 567-2757  
  
**HOW DO YOU COLLECT AND USE INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN UNDER       13 YEARS OF AGE??**

Pursuant to the provisions of the Federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we do not collect personal identifiable information from children under thirteen years of age without the consent of a parent or legal guardian.  Thus, when a guest under 13 years of age registers, he/she is required to provide the email address of his/her parent (or legal guardian).  We then contact the parent (or legal guardian) and alert them to the child’s registration.  We require the parent or guardian to validate the account in order for the potential member to become a registered member.  However, even after an account has been validated, no personally identifiable information collected from guests under the age of thirteen will ever be sold or provided to any third parties, or used for any marketing or promotional purposes. **  **In addition, parents may request to review the personally identifiable information collected from their child, may ask to have that information deleted, and may refuse to allow further collection or use of their child’s personally identifiable information at any time. To request such review or to give instructions regarding the personally identifiable information we have collected about a child, parents/legal guardians should contact us in one of the ways mentioned above in the section entitled “How do you opt out? How do you change the information we have for you?” or in the section below entitled "Questions? Contact Us." 

**THIRD PARTY LINKS, CO-BRAND RELATIONSHIPS, AND PUBLIC FORUMS**

In an attempt to provide increased value to our visitors, Broadband Sports may choose various third party web sites to link to, link from, and frame within, the Broadband Sports Network. Broadband Sports also participates in co-branding and other relationships to offer e-commerce and other services and features to its users. However, even if the third party is affiliated with Broadband Sports, we have no control over these linked sites, each of who have separate privacy and data collection practices independent of Broadband Sports. We have no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions, and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any such web sites. Please make sure you are comfortable with the privacy practices of every site you visit before providing the site with your personal information. These linked sites are only for your convenience and you therefore access them at your own risk.

We also make chat rooms, forums and message boards available to you on the Broadband Sports Network. Please remember that we cannot control the information that is shared by members and that anything you voluntarily provide in any public area of the Internet will be publicly available to other visitors on that web site and potentially to other third parties. Thus, please note that you should always exercise caution when deciding to publicly disclose any of your personal information in these and similar areas.

**YOUR CONSENT**

By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of information by Broadband Sports as set forth in this privacy statement. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what limited circumstances we disclose it. Continued access or use of the web site shall constitute your express acceptance of any modifications to this privacy statement.

**QUESTIONS? CONTACT US.**

If you have any questions about our privacy practices or your dealings with our site, please do not hesitate to contact:

Customer Service  
2120 Colorado Avenue, Suite 200  
Santa Monica, CA 90404  
(888) 567-2757  

**TERMS AND CONDITIONS**

Please also visit Broadband Sports’ [Terms and Conditions](http://www.broadbandsports.com/privacy/terms_and_conditions.shtml) establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of the Broadband Sports Network.
